PROFILE

I am currently a student at Rochester Institute of Technology pursuing my BS in Computing Security.

CONTACT

PHONE: 774-578-3435

EMAIL:

mtn6807@rit.edu

EXTRA-CURRICULAR

RITSEC Mentorship Program- A program run by the RITSEC club which helps underclassmen to learn more about security by pairing them with an upperclassman mentor

Cello Player- Played 5 years in high school orchestra and 2 years afterwards.

Brick Hack 2018- started code for a scheduling application (still in progress)

MICHAEL NEE

EDUCATION

Rochester Institute of Technology

2017 - current

Pursuing BS in Computing Security. Coursework includes: Computer Science 1&2, Routing and Switching, Network Services, Mechanics of Programming

Walpole High School

2013 - 2017 GPA 3.1

WORK EXPERIENCE

Grace Watson Dining Server

December 2017-May 2018

Worked during the school year. I was responsible for doing basic prep work, greeting people and serving food.

iD Tech Instructor

July 2018-August 2018

Taught LUA to children ages 10-13 and Computing Security to children ages 13-18. I was responsible for creating lesson plans and maintaining a safe environment.

Fat Straw Barista

September 2018-Current

Working during the school year. I am responsible for greeting people and making bubble tea drinks.

SKILLS

Programming Languages

Python, Java, C, Lua

Software

Microsoft Office, VMware, Cisco OS, Bash, Git